spireon.com 2019-09-29

# Privacy Policy - Spireon, Inc., The Vehicle Intelligence Company

Spireon is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Spireon, Inc. web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Spireon, Inc. web site, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
Spireon, Inc. collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Spireon, Inc. also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Spireon, Inc. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring web site addresses. This information is used by Spireon, Inc. for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Spireon, Inc. web site.

Mobile  
Spireon offers our customers the ability to find out what’s new with our products and services through their mobile device, either by browsing our mobile web site or through text messaging. Usage of the mobile web site follows similar standards employed by our standard web site; cookies may be employed to remember preferences or previous activity but do not reveal personal information and can be disabled using your mobile device’s Internet options. For text messaging, users will only receive messages if they have specifically opted in for them; standard text message rates will apply. To join Spireon Mobile, text the keyword “Spireon” to 774-53. To unsubscribe from Spireon, text the keyword “STOP” to 774-53.

Spireon, Inc. encourages you to review the privacy statements of web sites you choose to link to from Spireon, Inc. so that you can understand how those web sites collect, use and share your information. Spireon, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on web sites outside of the Spireon, Inc. and Spireon, Inc. family of web sites.

**USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
Spireon, Inc. collects and uses your personal information to operate the Spireon, Inc. web site and deliver the services you have requested. Spireon, Inc. also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Spireon, Inc. and its affiliates. Spireon, Inc. may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Spireon, Inc. does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Spireon, Inc. may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Spireon, Inc. may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Spireon, Inc., and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Spireon, Inc. does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Spireon, Inc. keeps track of the web sites and pages our customers visit within the Spireon, Inc. web site, in order to determine what Spireon, Inc. services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Spireon, Inc. to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Spireon, Inc. web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Spireon, Inc. or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Spireon, Inc.; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Spireon, Inc., or the public.

**USE OF COOKIES**  
The Spireon, Inc. web site uses “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Spireon, Inc‘s pages, or register with Spireon, Inc. site or services, a cookie helps Spireon, Inc. to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Spireon, Inc. web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Spireon, Inc. features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Spireon, Inc. services or web sites you visit.

**SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
Spireon, Inc. secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Spireon, Inc. secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**CONTACT INFORMATION**  
Spireon, Inc. welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Statement. If you believe that Spireon, Inc. has not adhered to this Statement, please email Spireon, Inc. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

**OTHER LEGAL NOTICES**  
Any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Statement and the Terms of Use, found on this web site, including limitations on damages and application of the law of the State of Tennessee. Spireon, Inc. will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect company and customer feedback. Please note that the use of information that Spireon, Inc. gathers is subject to the privacy notice in effect at the time of use. You should check the Spireon, Inc. web site frequently to see recent changes.
